{
    "stTableCheckBoxInit": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(1) > td.GLNOMTPDHM.GLNOMTPDEO.GLNOMTPDBP > div > span > img",
    "stTableCheckBoxRowEvenBack": ") > td.GLNOMTPDGM.GLNOMTPDEO > div > span > img",
    "stTableCheckBoxRowEvenFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableCheckBoxRowOddBack": ") > td.GLNOMTPDHM.GLNOMTPDEO > div > span > img",
    "stTableCheckBoxRowOddFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableContainerBackInfo": ") > td:nth-child(5) > div > table > tbody > tr > td.GLNOMTPDG5D > span",
    "stTableContainerBackType": ") > td:nth-child(5) > div > table > tbody > tr > td.GLNOMTPDF5D",
    "stTableContainerFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableContainerInit": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(1) > td:nth-child(5) > div > table > tbody > tr > td.GLNOMTPDG5D",
    "stTableDescriptionBack": ") > td:nth-child(3) > div",
    "stTableDescriptionFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableLocationBackInfo": ") > td:nth-child(6) > div > table > tbody > tr > td.GLNOMTPDG5D > span",
    "stTableLocationBackLocType": ") > td:nth-child(6) > div > table > tbody > tr > td.GLNOMTPDF5D",
    "stTableLocationFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableLotSerialBack": ") > td:nth-child(4) > div",
    "stTableLotSerialFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableProductBack": ") > td:nth-child(2) > span",
    "stTableProductFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableQAVBack": ") > td:nth-child(8) > div",
    "stTableQAVFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableQOHBack": ") > td:nth-child(7) > div",
    "stTableQOHFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableQRBack": ") > td:nth-child(9) > div",
    "stTableQRFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableZSMSHoldBackEven": ") > td.GLNOMTPDGM GLNOMTPDNO > div",
    "stTableZSMSHoldBackOdd": ") > td.GLNOMTPDHM GLNOMTPDNO > div",
    "stTableZSMSHoldFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableZSMSHoldInit": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(1) > td.GLNOMTPDHM.GLNOMTPDBP.GLNOMTPDNO > div"
}